





## Summary

Jump to Section

I want to put to use my creative skills, technologies that I am familiar with innovative thoughts that will benefit the Organization in the long run and also help me in building my professional career.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

# **Work Experience**

SabPaisa as Java Trainee Feb 2020 to Sep 2020

web Devloper using java spring boot jsp hibernate,micro services,rest api

HERE Solutions Indian Ltd

Jun 2019 to Jul 2019

Navigation Mapping Using Map Creator MUDRIKA SHAKDWIPEE

Web Wide Vision Infotech

Feb 2018 to Apr 2018

Creating website for UPES Civil Utsav (http://civilutsav.inworkinglink)
Creating website for the annual fest of the UPES Civil Department for its event registration HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT,PHP

^ Back to Top

#### Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from University of Petroleum and Energy Studies, Dehradun in 2020 PG: in 0

^ Back to Top

#### **IT Skills**

| Tr okino                               |         |           |                      |  |  |  |
|--|---------|-----------|----------------------|--|--|--|
| Skill Name                             | Version | Last Used | Experience           |  |  |  |
| Tableau DreamWeaver ,Xamp              |         |           |                      |  |  |  |
| Edipse,visual studio                   |         |           |                      |  |  |  |
| C,HTML ,JAVA,SPRING Boot,Hibernate,jsp | 2.2.x   | 2020      | 0 Year(s) 6 Month(s) |  |  |  |
| 100 1 111 1                            | 40.0    | 0000      | 0.1/ ( ) 0.84 (1 ( ) |  |  |  |

# 1

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. vvindows, Upuntu 18.U **ZUZU** U year(s) o iviontin(s)

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English  | Proficient  | ✓    | ✓     | ✓     |
| Hindi    | Expert      | ✓    | ✓     | ✓     |

^ Back to Top

## **Projects**

Project Title: qwikform Client: sabpaisa

Nature of Employment: Project Location: sabpaisa newDelhi

Role: Programmer

Team Size: 4 Role Description: Made changes according to the need as well as change in UI, Maintain the Code Project Details: implementing businesslogic like client on boarding, transaction status as well created run time table for

each and every new client using java core, spring boot

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Category: OBC - non-creamy Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

 ${\it Careers-About\,Us-Clients-Terms\,\&\,Conditions-FAQ's-Contact\,Us-Report\,a\,Problem-Site\,Map-Resources}$ Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Duration: Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.